# **Full Stack Developer & Content Creator**

GitHub || LinkedIn

Accomplished problem solver and creative expert with extensive experience building full stack platforms, scaling projects/platforms, as well as creating and deploying commercial imagery as content. Providing thought partnership, leading with expertise to advise and deliver for clients and employers. Demonstrating high learning agility, changing career while remaining focused on using existing mastery of skills in new and different contexts. Comfortable with high levels of ambiguity and self motivating. Enjoy working in fast paced environments, focused on delivering results, and excited by new and complex challenges.

# **CORE SKILLS**

Java	PostgresSQL	CI/CD
JavaScript	Sanity	Git
Python	Gatsby	GitHub
React.js	Cloud Architecture	NPM
Next.js	MicroServices	YARN
Node.js	Amazon Web Services	RESTful API's
Typescript	Nginx	Express
Redux	Blockchain(Stellar)	Webpack
Serverless	Stripe	ES6
Lambdas	HTML5	Responsive Design
DynamoDB	CSS5	Scrum framework
GraphQL	jQuery	Adobe PS & Al

### **EXPERIENCE**

## AIDONIC - Zug, Switzerland - June 2020 - July 2022

First to market, global web platform for the humanitarian aid space. Providing full transparency and accountability in crowdfunding and last mile aid distribution using Blockchain technology.

#### **Lead Software Engineer**

Recruited to evaluate MVP and bring to production at scale.

- Re-built most database architectures to allow for maximum efficiency and maintainability
- Expanded and optimized proprietary blockchain based last mile aide distribution tech stack
- Implemented CI/CD work flows and led the department in feature development and maintenance
- Worked with UI/UX designers to improve overall platform experience and feel
- Close partnership with CEO on tech stack evolution and feature prioritization. Providing modern knowledge of best practices and creative problem solving for business needs
- Winner "CUTTING-EDGE CREATIVITY" Award, Swiss Digital Economy Award 2021 Finalist, Swiss FIntech Finalist, The Europas 2020 Finalist, Top 20 Fintech Startups in Switzerland

#### BUSINESS OWNER: BEARDY STUDIOS, LLC - Global - Aug 2007 - August 2020

A full production commercial advertising, editorial & e-com photo/video studio.

### Owner / Full Stack Developer / Photographer

- Led in-house creative teams
- Sourced clients
- Worked directly with client creative leadership teams to create brand imagery/video content for ad campaigns, marketing and/or e-com
- Produced, created and delivered national and global advertising campaigns
- Build e-commerce platforms for fashion and real estate brands
- Key roles responsible for: Full Stack Developer, Photographer, Lighting Designer, Art Director, Producer, Retoucher, & Video Editor
- Clients Included: Aerosoles, Bloomingdales, Burt's Bees, Clorox, David Yurman, DKNY, Ebay, Lowe's Home, Improvement, Macy's, New York University, Ogilvy & Mather Agency, Theory/Helmut Lang, Victoria's Secret, Lowe's Home Improvement

## **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSITY OF BATH (May 2020 - present [graduation January 2023]) **MSc Computer Science** 

THINKFUL/BLOC - January 2019 - July 2019

Full Stack Developer Track

Learned industry best practices and practical software development standards with a focus on JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, React, Redux, HTML5, CSS3, algorithms & data structures. Created and deployed mobile-first applications while learning new languages and frameworks by collaborating several hours every week with a senior web developer.

TEXAS STATE UNIVERSITY - 2007 **BFA in Digital and Photographic Imaging** Graduated Cum Laude 3.8 GPA